

UX Designer - Design Researcher Sydney, NSW

About Me

I'm a User Experience Designer with a strong background in Health and Nutrition. I'm a natural problem solver and passionate about Human-Centered Designs, and I strongly believe that communication is key for building strong relationships with stakeholders and, as a result, coming up with better solutions.

Work Experience

IAG/Firemark Product Designer - APR 2022 - APR 2022

End-to-end Design Process.

- Exploring the viability and desirability of Parametric Insurance (Quickcover) Within 3 weeks, we delivered a Hi-Fidelity Prototype website for a new Insurance policy for Firemark.

In a team of 4, we implemented the Design Thinking Process (Double Diamond) to explore behaviour and motivations behind Insurance customers, to bring the Human-element to their new product with Human-centered Design approach.

Guardian Childcare & Education Chef/Nutritionist - JAN 2020 - JAN 2022

- Responsible for developing cooking classes and immersive cooking experiences;
- Built relationships with parents and children creating a safe environment and a fun experience for the children; Utilising empathy research I guided kids and parents through a healthier life style.

Industry Skills

Professional Skills

- Discover: UX Research
- Define: Synthesis
- Surveys
- Competitive &

Comparative Analysis

- Contextual Inquiry
- User Interviews
- Field Studies
- User observation
- Market analysis
- Affinity Mapping
- User scenarios
- Journey Mapping
- Personas & archetype
- User flows
- Information Architecture

Contact

- 0426 020 087
- kamille_poli@hotmail.com
- https://milliepoli.com/
- in https://www.linkedin.co/in/kamille-poli/

Education History

General Assembly - Sydney, NSW

UX Design Immersive

Full-time UX immersive course with 500+ hours of

Jan 2022 - professional workshops.
April 2022 Developed in-class

projects practising the design thinking process and utilising design tools

Estacio de Sa University - Brazil

Bachelor Degree in Nutrition

Jan 2010- Nutrition and dietetics skills,
JUL 2014 patient interviews, psychology

and storytelling.

Achievements

3 times winner "Guardian Gstar" Employee of the month at Guardian Childcare & Education

Design Tools

FIGMA MIRO SKETCH Trello

Ideation: Solution & Iteration

- Problem Solving
- Design Studio
- Sketchina
- Wireframe & Wireflows
- Usability Testing and A/B testing
- Prototyping

Deliver: Communicating with Client

- Presenting project
- Storytelling
- Feedback loops
- Product Analytics
- Working with a team